Love me,
loving love me love me Let me hear
end of the day I will be leaving
Let's see I'll turn the music
I'll be over I'll be over
I'll be over Love me Love me.
Do her stop and tell me.
Love me happy.
Stick up than what I do.
Love me Love me.
I'm so bahṣṇate.
Show me Tell me Tell me.
I love you, I love you
I
love
you,
I love you
I'm sorry, Itadori.
He's fast.
I can't figure out the
trick to his technique.
Now with him overwhelming me this badly,
he's not likely to reveal his hand.
I have no chance to use Convergence.
None of my external blood
manipulation is useable!
You're persistent.
Seriously, though, what are you?
An older brother with
nine younger siblings.
Flowing red scale. Stuck!
Good to know, but that's not what I asked.
I want to know why you're so tough.
and about that technique of yours.
He's starting to match me.
I see what he's up to.
Flowing red scale, huh?
He's focusing that power on his external
eye muscles to improve his kinetic vision.
You can't beat me.
I can counter your moves before
you even know you'll make them.
Since you're so persistent, I
went ahead and used my weapon.
Don't worry.
You can easily stop the bleeding
with your blood manipulation.
Let's find out how well you do fighting me
and staunching your
blood at the same time.
You came prepared with a sword.
Keep it a secret, will ya?
Honestly, I think it's lame.
A sorcerer walking around with a weapon?
It feels strange if you
can't win without it.
But a surprising number
of people think this way.
It's not just me.
I mean, I think my older brothers
are pathetic for caring them.
And yet they think they have some
kind of right to complain about Toji.
You hate them, don't you?
Your older brothers?
I do hate them.
Older brothers less competent than
younger brothers serve no purpose.
Actually, I think they
deserve to be hanged.
You should have gratitude towards them.
Your older brothers have
shaped who you are today.
Ah, that is the most disgusting
thing I have ever heard.
Please don't gross me out.
Whether or not older
brothers are competent,
they set an example for
their younger brothers.
If I make mistakes and
go down the wrong path,
then my little brothers
can avoid that path.
And if I go down the proper path, then
my little brothers can follow after me.
What would you do if you were strong
because your older brothers proved weak?
You ask me why I'm tough.
I'll tell you.
I never had an example.
I had to make many, many mistakes.
And yet, I kept walking in
front of my younger brothers.
And that made me strong.
What's he going on about, and how is
he still alive after bleeding so much?
The Death Paintings are
a mix of curse and human.
They possess the unique ability to
convert cursed energy into blood.
Until their cursed energy dries up,
they cannot die from blood loss.
Why are my legs heavy?
Did he harden the blood that
seeped into the fabric of my shoes?
Do you understand now?
This is checkmate.
Don't congratulate yourself yet.
My technique traces my opponent's
future motions at 24 frames per second.
This is only a minor hindrance,
and I can still move.
Who missed his chance?
Why isn't he striking out against me?
Developed after grappling with his technique
for over a hundred and fifty years,
this was a Choso original.
I'm sorry, but I can't understand
how you never loved your brothers.
That looks painful now. Yeah.
Don't look down on me.
What is this poison blood manipulation?
Shouldn't be capable of.
No.
It's not a product of this.
technique.
He had that much blood
because he's not human.
Could it be an incarnation?
Is his
inhuman blood in my body being rejected?
Shall I heal you?
I have reversed curse technique.
It can
heal people.
And then in return, could you please
report Itadori's death to the top brass,
as per our arrangement?
Yes, Father, what is it?
But if you want to talk about
her again, then I'm going home.
Look, Jin.
You're free to live your life
whichever way you choose.
However, you have to stay away
from that woman, or you'll die!
Please stop saying such terrible
things in front of Yuji, Father.
You'd be surprised at how
much a baby can remember.
I know that the most important
thing for you was to have a child,
and I'm sorry that you were
never able to do that with Kuroi.
But, son, Kuroi died, and you know I'm...
Now, father, why would you say that?
I'm alive. But how?
Oh, thank goodness.
It was September, I think.
Satoru Gojo went out of his way to see me.
He asked me to always watch after you.
So I had no choice but to put on that act.
You were acting?
I've got a bit of a bad feeling.
If anything happens to me,
I want you to take care of the
first and second year students.
Except for Hakari, he'll be fine.
If anything happens?
You in trouble with a woman?
I'm glad to see you've developed
a sense of humor, Yuta.
No, I'm serious.
I just can't imagine anything
happening to you, Gojo.
Well, just in case, take
special care of Yuji Itadori.
He's been sentenced to secret
execution like you were.
It would be a big help to me
if you looked out for him.
Oh, by the way, how's Miguel?
He said he didn't want to see you.
Eh?
This act was the best option to prevent
someone else from being sent to execute you.
And to cut off any information
about you to others as well.
Then again, they're not idiots either.
So before they would approve
me as the executioner,
headquarters made me forge a
pact to make sure I did it.
That's the reason I actually
had to kill you for a moment.
I'm real sorry about that
Wait, if you killed me,
then how am I still alive?
Reverse curse technique.
I used my reverse curse
technique the moment
your heart stopped to
immediately heal you!
I figured it would work based upon all
the things I've heard about you before.
I guess I was right.
There aren't too many
people around who know
that I'm capable of
outputting positive energy.
This is the second time
you faked your death.
They're bound to figure it out.
But the situation still chaotic.
They're going to believe
you're dead for a while.
At least headquarters will.
Think your death sentence was carried out.
Why go this far?
What's in it for you?
I'm doing it.
Because the people that I cherish also
happen to be people who cherish you.
The power I shoulder I used to think
it was greater than I could bear.
At first I thought the power
had been forced upon me.
But it was really something
that I'd brought upon myself.
I'm not like you.
The power you shoulder isn't yours.
It's not your fault.
That's not true.
You don't get it.
It isn't a matter of
who's to blame or not.
I killed them. It was me. It's a door.
Fushiguro?
What are you doing here?
We're going back to Jujutsu High.
The barrier surrounding the
school has been weakened.
It should be safe for you
to return there again.
so long as no one sees your face.
We'll meet up with the
upperclassmen and then...
Stop it!
Don't talk about it like
it's just another normal day.
Don't just pretend it didn't happen.
I killed people.
A lot of people.
It's because of me that
somebody are dead now!
Because of us!
Of course you would say that.
You can't give up
just because you want to.
We aren't heroes.
We're jjutsu sorcerers.
There's no one who can judge
us unless they've been us?
That's all the more reason why we
have to keep proving why we exist!
You're wrong, Fujiwara.
We don't have time to worry about
ourselves and our feelings anymore.
Don't say that.
We exist to save others.
You'll end up suffering.
I thought saving people was
your driving motivation.
The whole time you stay around me.
Start by saving me, Itadori.
Noritoshi Kamo has set up a death game
between those he granted curse techniques.
The Culling Game.
Tsumiki has been drawn into this game too.
Itadori, please.
I need your power.
Okotsu, I need your help.
Sukuna is plotting something
that uses Fushiguro.
He was able to take
over my body in Shibuya
after I was forced to
eat ten fingers at once.
There's now a total of
fifteen fingers inside of me.
Even if I'm fed the
remaining five all at once,
I don't think he'll be
able to take me over again.
But if he does, if Sukuna appears
and takes control of me again,
I need you to kill me.
Can I trust you to do that for me?
Yes, of course.
I promise I'll do it.
Okay, Fushiguro.
What do you need me to do?
First, we go back to Jujutsu High,
and then make contact with Tengen.
How can we release the
seal of the prison realm?
What is Noritoshi Kamo's actual
goal, and what moves will he make?
The Cullen Game is an unprecedented
act of Jujutsu terrorism,
and we need answers to those
questions to resolve this situation.
I think the Tengen might be the
only one capable of answering them.
What about that woman?
Maybe Tsukumo knows.
I've already spoken to Tsukumo.
In fact, this whole thing was her plan.
She's also hiding away at Jujutsu High.
Hiding away from what?
Apparently, she doesn't want
to deal with the higher-ups.
However, the problem is
Tengen's concealment barriers.
Within the barriers, there are a
thousand constantly shuffling doors.
Only one leads to the tombs of
the star where Tengen resides.
So unless we pick the right
door, we can't meet with Tengen?
I'm sorry, Fushikurl, but...
I need to ask you something.
What happened to Kugisaki?
I see.
All right.
All right I understand so about
the concealment barriers I
have a good workaround for that
How long has he been listening
What's the workaround tell
us you remember when Mode
stole Sukena's fingers and
the death with paintings,
we're going to do the same thing.
Well, it hasn't been that
long since the last time, huh?
Maki, what a surprise.
Oh, hello.
Maki, is it safe for you to be up?
Yeah, it's not a problem.
Not much I could do about the burns.
Reverse curse technique can erase scars.
I have to say, your heavenly pact
of physical prowess is impressive.
You saved your life with the
strength of your body's endurance.
You didn't put faith in your
resistance to curses alone.
That's a shame the clan
head didn't make it.
It's not like it was a
competition or something.
Megumi, how's it going
with Tengen's barrier?
Well, you see, let me explain.
On the way to the Tombs of the
Star, it's the Forbidden Vault.
Inside that vault are Jujutsu-hai's
cursed tools and cursed objects,
plus the remains of my brothers.
Nuran-so, Choso, Tan-so,
Seance, Kotsu-so, and Choso.
Even though it's just their remains,
I should be able to sense their presence
using the side effect of my technique.
Good for you.
That's really great to
hear, but who are you?
Well for now I guess you can
call him my older brother.
Let's go.
That's the one I'm
certain of it my younger
brothers are resting
right beyond this door.
I'm opening it.
Let's head down.
Further in, there's an elevator
leading to the tombs of the star.
Choso!
Coming.
I'll come back for you later.
Hang in there a little longer.
Bloodstains?
I wonder what happened.
It was 12 years ago.
Thinking back on it now, that's
when all the distortion started.
Can't just be a coincidence, can it?
All right, everyone.
The main hall is just up ahead.
There's nothing here.
This is the main hall.
No.
He's declining to speak with us.
Tengen won't interfere with reality.
I thought if there was ever a
chance to reach him it would be now.
All the six eyes are sealed away.
I was obviously naive.
It's not all of us being
rejected but just me.
We should head back.
Tsumiki doesn't have time to spare.
Leaving so soon?
It's nice to meet you, child of Zenin,
descendant of Michizane, cursed
wound death painting, and at last...
It's the vessel of Sukuna.
I must impose one condition.
We came here to learn how
to open the prison route.
No greeting for me?
Then why is this calling game?
To force the evolution of mankind.
It's better for the rules if
being stripped means death, too.
If Sukuna takes control again,
don't hesitate to kill me.
Don't die out there.